Yes, we have a live delivery.
It's been a long time since I've done a live broadcast, so I'm going to get into it...
Not a shhh?
Shhh.
Let's get into it.
Shut up.
No, I'm just saying, let's get into it.
You say that?
Then, Kaneichi, please.
Please... 5 seconds.
Balicata Prefecture...
Of course you went there with your family during summer vacation.
Yes, I did.
I'm sure it's hard to fit it into your schedule now.
What kind of places do people from Kyushu go with their families?
What kind of places do they go?
For example...
Mt. Fuji.
Camping...
Aso.
Kumamoto.
Beppu?
Beppu.
BPU.
Beppu
BPU
Beppu BPU.
I haven't been able to go to any of those lately.
Yeah.
I haven't been to those places.
I go back to Fukuoka sometimes.
I go back to Fukuoka, but I don't go to other places in Kyushu.
I don't get to go to other places in Kyushu even when I'm on tour as Ebitu.
That's right.
By the way...
The other day you were on tour with Ebituju and you finally returned to Fukuoka.
You know, the triumphant return to Fukuoka?
Yes, there was.
How was it?
It was fun.
It was different... from other places.
It feels like home.
It felt like home.
I felt like my family was watching.
Until now.
I don't always feel that mysterious tension.
It's cool to make a triumphant return.
I'm also in some way... Good evening.
I'm triumphant in Mitaka city... why do I have to be triumphant?
No, no, no, no, that's why...
You know... he's a very famous family man.
He's a very famous family man.
Thank you very much.
That feels great! Take care of your family!
We sometimes go there during summer vacation.
Yes, we do.
We have a family get-together once a month for dinner.
Wow, I can't think of anything like that.
In my family, it's just that each one of us does what we want to do.
It's not that my mother and I want to do that kind of thing, and we've been doing whatever we want.
It's true that we didn't do anything as a family until the early grades of elementary school, but it was much earlier.
When it's summer vacation, students have to do something with their friends.
It's not easy to go out with family.
It's embarrassing to go out with family.
That's what I mean.
It's true, I'm at an age.
I've been an old man since then.
I'm still like that.
It's like a long adolescence.
I've been in puberty my whole life.
That's great.
I've been an adolescent for over a quarter of a century, so I've always had the mind of a boy.
Boy, I mean... I've been an adolescent forever.
Forever adolescent.
You know, Barrigata said that my brother doesn't care about me.
He really doesn't care.
Did he come to your return to Fukuoka?
He came. I mean, my parents brought me.
He said he'd go.
Did you talk to him? After it was over?
No.
He didn't say anything about it when I had shrimp in my hand.
And after the show, too.
I was sleepy. What does he see in you, then?
I see... my own sister...
It's amazing that you don't feel anything when you see your own sister singing and dancing.
I don't think you were looking at me when you saw her perform.
You look at the other girls and think...
Oh, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
I don't think she's looking at me.
Well, on the other hand, I don't think she's all that interested in you.
That's true.
That's a little scary, too.
As a boy... I see.
I guess that's part of it.
Let's go to the mail today.
What kind of guy are you?
He looks like a kindergartener, but he's an old man.
It's Conan! The new Conan!
Conan! By the way...
Conan... by the way... there was some talk about this being like an EbiChu tour...
She's still touring, right?
We're still on tour.
The final show will be at the end of July, right?
July 28th.
That's a long time.
It's still a little while.
Are you going to say goodbye to the band in the middle of the tour?
No, no, no.
Even if I did, I wouldn't tell you.
Yes, yes, yes.
By the way...
By the way... the blue Mars in Nakahara, Kawasaki...
He sent it to me.
He was accompanying Ebitu on her spring tour.
Principal Fujii's appearance
He looked like the mascot of a TV show about discovering the wonders of the world.
so I made an illustration of it.
titled Fujii-kun doll.
Learning to be a boss
Like a boss Fujii-kun.
So this is what a principal looks like?
Is he like this?
He's like an explorer.
You look like an explorer.
I was dressed like this just the other day.
At last?
It's time.
I was wearing a haunted feather and glasses as usual.
He said, "You look like an explorer.
Why did you suddenly become an explorer?
I'm not sure when this movie was made.
Taipei, I think. It was last weekend.
It was too hot.
If you were on an expedition, you'd be wearing short sleeves and a short pants.
I was wearing a Bakeha.
You're a great principal.
He's got a set.
You're holding a hammer?
I do! He's got a shoulder strap and a gold finger.
We'll have a chance to play "kon-kon-kon.
You're building a stage too?
That's amazing.
Yes, yes, yes.
And I'll tell you what else I'm going to do during my summer vacation...
I don't think you'll be doing that.
Do you know the Kurobe Dam?
A dam?
Yes, a dam.
If it's Kurobe, I'll say "dam".
If it's not a dam, I'll ask you to write down the name.
It's a dam, but it's a very famous dam.
I think I've done it before.
It was very difficult to build, and it was located deep in the mountains of Nagano and Toyama, but the dam was built a long time ago, so it was a rare and difficult project in the history of Japanese construction.
The dam was built deep in the mountains of Nagano and Toyama, and it was one of the most difficult constructions in the history of Japanese construction.
A lot of movies have been made about it, including "Kurobe no Taiyo" (The Sun of Kurobe) and Yujiro Ishihara's movie "Kurobe no Taiyo.
It is such a legendary dam that it has been the subject of many movies.
Of course, it still exists today.
The night commuter train sent it to me.
Thank you very much.
I went to Kurobe Dam.
So...
I've been there a few times.
I've been there several times.
Kurobe Dam is huge!
It's built like this to warn the public.
So it's very high.
And there is a little...
I don't know how to say it.
So that you can feel fear.
There is a staircase.
For example, Tokyo Tower has stairs, right?
That's right.
Just like that.
So that you can see how high it is.
That's right.
As a matter of fact
I'm afraid of heights, too.
Let's try it, Master!
So...
First of all, I'd like you to show Balikata the whole view of Kurobe Dam.
This, this, this...
This is it, this is it, this is it!
It's really amazing!
And here, people can see it from here...
Oh, oh, scary!
You can do something.
You can't see the bottom here.
But it's really high up.
Wow!
And there's a staircase on the side here.
And there's a staircase attached to the side of the building, where the public can cook.
It's like this... a staircase.
But the view is beautiful... and the air is fresh.
I'm just leaning forward to stop this story from becoming what it would be if I took a picture of it and made an Odam...
Is that what you're saying?
I can understand why there are dam maniacs.
When you look at the construction...
I like dams, even though I'm a bit of a height freak.
What is it?
A dam is like a Gundam, isn't it?
Yes, like the one below.
Like a "dun-dun-dun".
Dum-dum!
We're in the same dam group.
You don't like dams, do you?
It's a Gundam, isn't it?
That's why he's included.
This is a human being, isn't it?
In terms of the staircase...
You can see here from this staircase.
When you come to this point...
You can see Morocco right below.
The water is falling down, and this is falling down, and this is falling down, and this is up to the top, and the water is falling down, and it's almost down to the very bottom.
That's why I've been talking about the Kurobe Dam for a long time.
I can't go up the stairs!
This one's no good!
If it's off, it'll be like this.
If I have to go up there...
Don't look this way, don't look at the scary side!
You have to go to the wall like this.
Look at the wall like this.
Sometimes I'd do a "boom" and say, "That's not a wall-banging!
Like this... and then boom...
This is not the time for wall-banging.
I see.
Then you can afford it.
You're saying that now, but...
But I don't really do that.
Let's check it out.
I don't think he'll say anything.
Or maybe he'll say something really loud.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You hate him that much, don't you, Takai?
I'm just saying...
Thank you for all the public service Ministry of Education people.
I'm totally fine.
I don't think you understand.
I don't think you'd understand, but people in the Ministry of Education are...
I'm sure you don't understand, but the Ministry of Education is a scary place.
And you say, "I'll go if I understand.
It's not that I don't understand, but it happens all the time.
Like, "Do it.
Even if I say I'll go...
But my body won't go against my will, probably because of fear, and it feels like my body is telling me to stop.
My legs won't go forward, so I can't help it.
It's like, "Yay." Can you speak? Yes, yes, yes.
So we'll probably be yelling "yay" at each other at the bottom of the stairs the whole time.
I'm sure you'll be angry about that, too.
Speaking of heights, I bungee jumped during my two-week vacation.
What? Where?
At Mother Farm. Shingo and I went there for a YouTube shoot.
You know, the jump platform?
It was my first time bungee jumping there.
It's really scary, but I did it.
We went up there and jumped the signal.
So I'm just making sure it's safe.
I'd already jumped once, so I knew it wouldn't cut it.
And the second time, I went up and jumped backwards.
I went like this. I went like this.
But I was really scared.
But it's fun. Bungee jumping is really fun.
It was really good. You can go bungee jumping, right? It's not that expensive.
No, no, no, that's not the point. I'll probably go up to the top of the stairs.
I think I'll stop on my own on the way. Did you see that? I'm like, "Did you see that? No, really, really. That's the only thing.
Isn't bungee jumping funny?
It's crazy.
What's the point of it?
Who benefits from it?
It's just for fun.
If you're going to do something like that for fun.
There are so many other things to do.
That's why we have Bungy.
Because it's fun.
There are so many other fun things to do in this world!
Why don't we all just do it?
Why don't you just play games on your cell phones?
There's fun to be had with Bungy, isn't there?
Wait a minute.
You've done it before?
Bungy? More like sky-jumping.
Diving?
No, it's more like a jump, a sky jump.
It's like, you know, you go up from, like, 190, 180 meters.
You go up and down.
What? What does that mean?
There's a string or a wire or something like that.
It's like a wire that goes down.
From the top of the building.
What?
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that?
What a saga!
That's a lot more than a bungee.
That's quite a saga all of a sudden.
What?
You're going to go to the top of a building?
No, it's more like a building.
Like a tower.
There's a circle around the outside of the building.
You walk there.
And then you fly.
Oh, that's different from bungee?
It's not like a bungee.
It's like this, but the cord is a straight cord.
What?
The cord is straight down.
You hold it with a swoosh and go down.
Oh, I see! So you fall down, like this.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Shoe...
It doesn't bounce around like a mimey.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Like a stick that firemen use to get off in a hurry.
It's like a stick that firemen use to get off.
Wow!
But you don't like it?
Awww...
It's the same thing, isn't it?
I can't do this.
You're right.
I mean, before you go there, you feel like this...
Oh, it's like, "Oh, it's like, "Oh, it's like that.
And down...
Down...
I can see you, can't I?
It's fun, isn't it?
I'm sure it's not thrilling at all... but it's a great idea... 190 meters.
It's like a five- or seven-story building... like the Mother Farm... only seven floors above the ground.
So it's 190 meters. I don't know what that means.
I think it's about that high.
It's a very long way down.
So it's not like it's free-falling... there's some kind of stopper here or something...
It's not like it's just going to fall down, it's just going to fall down, but it's going to fall down.
But it's already 180 or 190, so it takes a long time.
It takes longer than holding it.
I don't want to be like that all the time... that's scary... it's kind of free-falling, isn't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I can eat bugs.
And you can break a lie. Yes, yes, yes, you can break a lie.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
The other day, when Harunosuke Tachikawa was here, he asked me what my favorite food was.
I asked him what his favorite food was.
I said, "Natto and Lipolytan D mixed together would be good.
Lipovitan D? It's not Neapolitan!
Ripolitan D, Ripodi, Ripo... how do you say it? Lipovitan D.
Lipo... not a word... you said you wanted to mix Lipo D with it.
Someone heard about it and immediately did it.
Thank you very much, Mr. Yoshio from Yamanashi Prefecture!
Thank you very much for your voice in Yamanaka this year as well.
Why, Mr. Nakamura, the other day...
The other day...
I named it "Natto Vitan D".
Natto Vitan D
Natto and Lipody mixed together...
Just in case you don't like the picture, you might not like this.
Oh, really?
I'm a little bit scared of it. It's like...
It's a little too graphic.
Oh, no!
You put natto in the water.
Yeah, that's why I put natto in it and poured it out, I think.
I didn't put it in the bag, I put it in the cup like sauce.
I put it in the cup.
I don't know if he drank it or ate it.
I don't know if he ate it or drank it, but he tried it.
And his impression was
The protein of the natto and the dark sweetness of the beverage
and the sweetness of the beverage intertwine and directs you to taste them separately.
It was a good experience.
I'll have to give it a try.
I have to try it.
We're going to try it.
You have to try it and hope it tastes better.
Food...
People eat all kinds of food, but...
But at first, I think there were a lot of combinations that people didn't like. I think there were a lot of combinations.
A typical example is...
Strawberry Daifuku.
You always say that, don't you?
I didn't have that when I was in elementary school.
It was only in high school that they came out with a new product called "Strawberry Daifuku".
They came out with a new product called "Strawberry Daifuku.
Everyone treats it like it's a ghetto.
It's disgusting! or something like that.
It's so delicious!
Back then, it was much, much rougher than it is now.
Like now.
Now you've got a match!
You're a match! It's like, "Here's Match!
Here comes Match!
Boom! DASSS! It's like, "Here comes Mr. Match!
But back then, it was really Daifuku.
I put strawberries instead of Daifuku.
We put strawberries in place of Daifuku?
Like, "We put strawberries in place of Daifuku.
It was like, "Wow!
It was like, "Anko (red bean paste) flavor and strawberries don't go well together," but now it's become a regular product.
But now it's a standard item.
That's why there are so many of them.
So maybe Natto Bittandi will be around in a few years.
They won't do it in a few years? You know...
Not yet.
Natto is necessary? Maybe it will be the norm.
Maybe, maybe not.
Thank you for experiencing it firsthand.
Balikata, are you adventurous? Like food?
No, I can't. I can't.
I told him that you don't eat bugs if you can't.
I was kind of poking around in my mind.
But you can eat bugs.
I don't know what it is.
I think there might be something different from us in the genes of Balikata that eats insects.
He's 17 years old, so he's a little different from me.
We've been taught that we shouldn't eat bugs, so it's hard to change that now.
I'm at a loss.
Well, I have an announcement for those of you who are watching the live broadcast.
It's the YT Devil's Original Jigsaw Puzzle!
So, this time...
Well, this is just a sample...
It's a sample, right? It's like a puzzle.
It's already cut into small pieces.
And this, for your enjoyment, is also included, this pure white one.
And you can draw your own picture on it.
You can draw your own picture on it.
If you can complete the puzzle and send it to us...
If you send it to us...
We'll take a look at it and say
We'll look at it and think it's really cool.
We think it's really cool and we'll make it our own.
First of all, there is a master show.
The show that I thought was really cool.
The show that the master thought was really cool.
And then there's the Nakajima Raiya Show, which is my show.
I'm going to choose one that I think is great.
And there's also a show by Ebichu, so I'll have Ebichu make a decision.
And each of you will get a nice present?
Yes, we do.
I'll put in a 500 yen QUO card.
It's the same for everyone, right?
You can go. Can I go?
I'm going to... Oh, my God.
I'll draw a portrait of the winner.
But, you see, I'm not looking at a photo, of course.
I'm imagining it from a pen name.
Imagine from the name.
I'll imagine it, and then I'll add a few words.
I'll give it to you. With a clip.
I'll also give you a Devil's Staff T-shirt.
The Yura Nakajima Award, by the way.
Yes, sir.
This one goes to you, too.
They're all saying one thing each.
That's the one you all get, isn't it?
The one written by each of you.
That's right.
Plus a Devil's Staff T-shirt.
Yes, yes, yes.
And that's the one for you, too, Ebitu.
Write your portrait.
If it's the Master's award, he writes it.
If it's my award, I'll write it.
If it's for Mr. Ebichu, then Mr. Ebichu will do it.
If it is Mr. Ebichu, then Mr. Ebichu will write it for you.
By the way, we're taking reservations at the TVK mall.
From 12th to 12th.
From 12th to 12th
23:59
July 12?
Yes.
We will accept your application until 23:59 on
Yes, sir.
If it's 23:59:10 or something like that, it's already dead.
No, that's it, isn't it?
Yes, that's it.
Oh, no.
Who has that kind of last minute crisis?
You know, with work and all.
Oh, I see.
Oh, shit! Oh, no!
But there's a huge window of time.
23:59:18
I'm going to have to decline.
I'll get it.
So, let's do it early.
So please make your reservation as soon as possible.
Please make a reservation.
That's all I can say.
Yes, sir.
You know who has a birthday recently?
Yes.
Anyone?
Lastly...
Oh.
Oh?
Is that him?
Because...
There's a month for every day.
Every day is a birthday.
You're gonna take that hat.
And throw it in the Ohara River?
Really.
November.
That's a long way.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Where's the master?
May.
And the balicata, by the way?
Maybe a double?
A birthday party.
It's a double birthday party.
No, it's not.
Can you stop making that really confused face?
I did it, Master.
Like we're going to do it again.
No, I won't.
I'm not going to do it again.
Don't fuck with me, man, don't fuck with me.
So Barigata is 17 on her birthday.
I turned 17!
Congratulations!
Wow! Devil's Charge is here too!
Thank you so much!
I heard your birthday party was great!
I really wanted to be there.
I really wish I could have been there, but we were just recording or something.
That's right.
Last year and this year, I'm always on the same day as Deville.
Harassment.
What?
I'm doing the birthday party by myself.
I do all the MC work.
I'm really interested in what he'll say.
I'm curious.
Are you going to laugh?
Or are you suddenly reading poems?
It's too sudden.
You can do whatever you want, right?
I don't care what you do.
But it's great.
By all means, next time, or next year?
Yes, next year.
I'd love to see it.
As is customary with DeVille...
I have prepared a birthday present for you!
But...
After all...
Even if I give it to you now...
It's not a very exciting show, is it?
Well, well, well...
Here's a sample that's up right now.
By the end of the live broadcast...
If you can get it assembled by the end of the live broadcast.
I'd like to give you a gift.
How hard can it be?
It's 300 pieces. 300?
Yes, sir.
It's broken like this. 300. Can you do it now?
Is that too much to ask? Please!
Can you do it?
Yes! We did it!
Congratulations!
You got the tample! Yes!
That was too fast.
No, no, no, no...
What the hell!
Don't be lickety-split!
If that was the original plan...
Master, you shouldn't have shown us the sample in the first place.
Really?
Did you already know that?
I didn't.
Dream Yoshida-san and I were so nervous.
Like, "You're going to show that to him.
You know what I'm talking about.
I explained it to you 10 minutes ago.
That's right.
It's almost the same thing, isn't it?
You did, didn't you?
They showed me.
That's not why I'm here.
Thank you very much.
This way, please.
Now, let's see what's inside.
Open the package.
What a farce, they say.
That's right.
It's a travesty, isn't it?
You're absolutely right.
I could do this in a second.
It was so fast.
Pang, pang, pang...
I don't know, there's always the possibility of turning it upside down, like this.
Yeah, two one-thousandths of a second.
Say, "Okay.
What?
That's not right.
Oh, shit.
Oh, this way.
We're live until the end of the show.
It's not going in.
It's done.
I can do it in less than 10 seconds.
Okay, I'll leave it at that.
What's that? That's it! That's an Air Jordan!
That's a tree!
What?
What is it?
Oh! Cool!
Jordan Air Jordan shoes.
Oh, my God!
They're basketball-esque.
Cute!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Congratulations!
Even Barrica seems to like basketball.
No, that's not what I meant.
Is there a reason for this?
I don't know.
Does it look good on me?
I'm sure it does.
I'm glad
Thank you.
Gross!
It's nice.
It's good.
What are you, Charisse?
Are you kidding me?
I thought you didn't look good.
You say funny things. You're a blabbermouth, so do something about it.
What the hell, don't answer something that's just plain weird.
Let me read you your debut charge
Congratulations, Mr. Unknown IKAI and Mr. Balikata!
Congratulations on getting your phone back.
Thank you.
And, mNagaoka-san, it's called a balicata happy bar!
Thank you very much!
bisco, congratulations again on your balicata!
Momoshiki-san
Barricutter and his 17th birthday. It's a parody of Harry Potter!
Happy birthday to Mr. Devilch!
And Mimichin, Happy Birthday to Bali Cutter!
Kahikahiho, happy birthday to Bali cutter!
Happy Birthday to Mr. Kahikahiho Bali Cutter! Happy Birthday to Mr. Kahikahiho Bali Cutter!
Happy Birthday, Tamamin! Happy Birthday, Bali Cutter!
Happy 17th Birthday, Mr. Caribon!
I've been waiting for the first Balinese in the new year!
I'm Barry.
I'll take it, I'll take it, I'll take it.
Isn't this your first time since you turned 17?
It's my first time. It's my first time at Debiri.
Whenever we have a two-shot party, I'm sure you'll ask for a balikbayan miss.
I get a lot of requests.
I get so many requests.
It's true, even Takeshi-san wants to ask you to do a comanage.
You can't say that to Takeshi-san, can you?
Other guests also came, including Mr. Playbody, who danced with us.
We have money for repairing Balikata-chan's phone!
Oh! Thank you very much.
I'm sure you think that's a lot. You're all so kind.
Natto Lipobee!
We have a Devil's Charge for the challenge.
Mr. Yuuhi Zadar applauds your spirit of challenge!
I mean to Yoshio!
New viewers and viewer to viewer.
We can't send it directly to Yoshio.
we will put it to good use in some way.
Thank you very much.
And Sakura-san.
I would like to congratulate you on your first live delivery in a long time.
And to see how the Devil members are doing.
We have received the Devil's Charge!
Thank you very much!
And Master's bungee jump!
Thank you very much.
Donation for Kikin! Donation for Kikin!
Mr. Momoshiki wants us to fly.
Don't be stupid, Momoshiki.
Don't you dare! Don't you dare! Don't you dare!
I'm sure they'll tell you to do it on the show.
But you know... my personality is such that if I can do it, even a little...
I'd do it, but he's really immobile.
I'll carry him in my arms because his legs are really stuck.
Something I don't know... some special force is at work.
Something I don't know, something that tells me not to do it.
It's really stuck?
No, it's really stuck.
If you try to move it, I'll do something violent!
You have a will, don't you?
There's a special force at work.
It moves on its own.
I'm scared.
That's why it can't be helped.
Unfortunately...
Well, well, well...
I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m. for the live broadcast.
Same time, 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for this week.
Thank you very much.
See you next week.
Congratulations.